A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records xFA250
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Press Releases, 1973-1977; 13; 27 Cubic Feet 15 Boxes
  - April 29, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    Washington, DC, Shoreham Hotel, Remarks at Annual Convention of Garden Clubs of America
  - April 29, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 138)
    Washington, DC, Shoreham Hotel, Press Conference following remarks at Garden Clubs of America
  - May 1, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 139)
    Washington, DC, Sheraton Carlton Hotel, Remarks and excerpts at National Urban Coalition
  - May 1, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - May 1, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - May 1, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - May 1, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 143)
    Press Release re: appointment of Governor Raymond P. Shafer as Counselor to Vice President
  - May 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 144)
    Statement on death of Kenneth Keating
  - May 6, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 145)
    Washington, DC, Madison Hotel - VP's Remarks to Institutional Investors Institute - Off-The-Record
  - May 9, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 146)
    Hot Springs, Virginia, Press Conference at Business Council
  - May 9, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 147)
    Hot Springs, Virginia, Remarks at Business Council
  - May 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 148)
    Remarks of C. Douglas Dillon following CIA Commission Meeting
  - May 16, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 149)
    Washington DC, Mayflower Hotel, Excerpts and remarks at National Republican Heritage Group Council
  - May 16, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - May 16, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 151)
    Press Conference following National Republican Heritage Group Council
  - May 16, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 152)
    Washington, DC, Mayflower Hotel, Q&A following National Republican Heritage Group Council
  - May 20, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 153)
    Washington, DC, Russell House Office Building, Remarks at Congressional Black Caucus Forum on Employment and excerpts from remarks
  - May 20, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - May 21, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 155)
    Remarks at Award Ceremony Recording for the Blind, EOB
  - May 21, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 156)
    House Office Building, Q&A following Bull Elephants Luncheon
  - May 21, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 157)
    House Office Building, Remarks at Bull Elephant Luncheon
  - June 2, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 158)
    Remarks during CIA Commission Meeting
  - June 4, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 159)
    Annapolis, Maryland, Remarks and excerpts at U.S. Naval Academy
  - June 4, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - June 4, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 161)
    Press Release re announcement by VP and Senator Kennedy on White House Science Advisory Conference
  - June 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 162)
    Press advisory re: allegations of CIA involvement assignations
  - June 6, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 163)
    Statement re: White House Science Advisory Conference, New Senate Office building
  - June 6, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 164)
    Washington, DC, National Press Building, Remarks to Delta Sigma Chi
  - June 10, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 165)
    Washington, DC, Rayburn House Office Building, Remarks before House Science Technology Committee
  - June 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 166)
    New York City, Waldorf Astoria Hotel, Remarks to New York State Republican Committee
  - June 15, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 167)
    Connie Chung interview of VP on Air Force II
  - June 24, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 168)
    Announcement re: Ann Whitman's return to New York City
  - June 26, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 169)
    Press release re: appointment of Quincy Rodgers
  - July 9, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 170)
    Atlanta, Georgia, Remarks and excerpts at National Commission on Water Quality
  - July 10, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 171)
    Joint Cabinet Briefing with President Ford and VP
  - July 10, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 172)
    East Room, White House, Remarks to Conference of Mayors
  - July 14, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 173)
    Washington, DC, Remarks at Awards Ceremony for Colonel Jack Walker
  - July 22, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 174)
    Q&A at Midwestern Governor's Conference
  - July 22, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 175)
    Cincinnati, Ohio, Netherlands Hilton Hotel, Press Conference
  - July 22, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 176)
    Remarks at Cincinnati Midwest Governors Conference
  - July 31, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 177)
    Press Release re: appointment of Larry Heath as Counselor to Vice President
  - August 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 178)
    Washington, DC, Gallaudet College, Excerpts of remarks at World Conference on the Deaf
  - August 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 179)
    Remarks to White House Summer Interns
  - August 6, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 180)
    Austin, Texas, Press Release re: Hospital Productivity Center
  - August 11, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 181)
    Press Release re: Admiral's House parties
  - August 26, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 182)
    Mobile, Alabama, Press Conference
  - August 26, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 183)
    Mobile, Alabama, Remarks at dinner of the Lt. Governors Conference
  - August 27, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 184)
    Columbia, South Carolina, Press Conference (2:40 p.m.)
  - August 27, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 185)
    Columbia, South Carolina, Remarks at Lace House
  - August 27, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 186)
    Columbia, South Carolina, Remarks at GOP Reception
  - August 27, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 187)
    Columbia, South Carolina, TV taping with Ed Rowland, Fred McNeese, Jan Stucker
  - August 27, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 188)
    Columbia, South Carolina, Press Conference (8:58 p.m.)
  - August 29, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 189)
    Warsaw, New York, Attica Grand Jury News Conference
  - September 2, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 190)
    Notice to Press re: housewarming events at Admiral's House
  - September 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 191)
    Rochester, New York, Press Conference
  - September 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 192)
  - September 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 193)
    Rochester, New York, Remarks at U.S. Chamber of Commerce Luncheon
  - September 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 194)
    Rochester, New York, Remarks at NY Chairman's Club Reception
  - September 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 195)
    Greece, New York, Remarks at Park Ridge Hospital
  - September 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 196)
    Rochester, New York, Remarks at J. Wholler Farm Center
  - September 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 197)
  - September 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 198)
    Morrilton, Arkansas, Remarks at Winrock Farm Reception
  - September 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 199)
    Dallas, Texas, Remarks at Dallas Republican Women's Convention
  - September 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 200)
    Dallas, Texas, TV Taping at Communication's Center
  - September 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 201)
    Dallas, Texas, Press Conference at Sheraton-Dallas
  - September 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 202)
    Little Rock, Arkansas, Press Conference at Airport Sheraton Motor Inn
  - September 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 203)
    Little Rock, Arkansas, private residence
  - September 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 204)
    Little Rock, Arkansas, Remarks at Winrock Farm
  - September 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 205)
    Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, Remarks at Tinker Air Force Base
  - September 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 206)
    Norman, Oklahoma, Remarks at residence of J. Blacks
  - September 13, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 207)
    Enid, Oklahoma, Remarks at Vance Air Force Base
  - September 13, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 208)
    Enid, Oklahoma, Remarks at Oakwood City Club
  - September 13, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 209)
    Enid, Oklahoma, Remarks at Republican Committee Dinner
  - September 15, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 210)
    London, England, Remarks at U.S. Bicentennial Exhibit
  - September 17, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 211)
    Washington, DC, National Archives Reading is Fundamental
  - September 18, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 212)
    Washington, DC, State Department, National Academy of Science Lunch
  - September 24, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 213)
    Washington, DC, Statement at Presentation of Public Occurrences
  - September 29, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 214)
    Washington, DC, Transcript at Federal City Council Meeting
  - September 29, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 215)
    Washington, DC, Remarks and Press Releases at Federal City Council Meeting
  - September 29, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 216)
  - October 2, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 217)
    Washington, DC, Remarks at Energy Conference Lunch
  - October 2, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 218)
    Portland, Oregon, Remarks at Hilton Hotel
  - October 3, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 219)
    Portland, Oregon, Remarks at Luncheon for Publishers
  - October 3, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 220)
    Portland, Oregon, Remarks at Republican Conference Dinner
  - October 6, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 221)
    Washington, DC, Remarks at Energy Conference
  - October 6, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 222)
  - October 7, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 223)
    Kings Mountain, North Carolina, Remarks at Joe Gamble Stadium
  - October 7, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 224)
    Washington, DC, White House Press Release - Vice Presidential Seal -- by President Ford
  - November 2, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 225)
    New York City, New York, Remarks on Issues and Answers
  - November 3, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 226)
    Washington, DC, Withdrawal Announcement From 1976 Presidential/Vice Presidential Ticket
  - November 5, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 227)
    Washington, DC, Address by VP to Staff
  - November 6, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 228)
    Washington, DC, Remarks before US Chamber of Commerce Group
  - November 6, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 229)
    Washington, DC, Press Conference Regarding Withdrawal decision
  - November 10, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 230)
    En route to Austin Texas, aboard Air Force II Press Conference of Vice President
  - November 10, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 231)
    Austin, Texas, Remarks at Conference of Women in Public Life
  - November 11, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 232)
    Austin, Texas, Remarks in Tiffany Ballroom
  - November 11, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 233)
  - November 11, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 234)
  - November 11, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 235)
    Austin, Texas, Remarks TV Taping, Capital Eye Program
  - November 14, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 236)
    Kansas City, Missouri, Remarks at Future Farmers of American group
  - November 14, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 237)
    Kansas City, Missouri, Remarks at Kansas City Auditorium
  - November 14, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 238)
    Kansas City, Missouri, Remarks of VP at Signal Hall
  - November 14, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 239)
    Lincolnshire, Illinois, Remarks at Lincolnshire Marriot
  - November 14, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 240)
    Lincolnshire, Illinois, Remarks at McClory Testimony Dinner
  - November 14, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 241)
  - November 15, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 242)
    Minneapolis, Minnesota, TV Taping at Registry Hotel
  - November 15, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 243)
  - November 15, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 244)
    Minneapolis, Minnesota, Remarks at Metropolitan Club Lunch
  - November 15, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 245)
    Minneapolis, Minnesota, Q & A at Minn. Metro Club
  - November 15, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 246)
    St. Cloud, Minnesota, Remarks at Minnesota Republican State Convention
  - November 15, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 247)
    St. Cloud, Minnesota, Remarks at Bicentennial Promotion Center
  - November 15, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 248)
    St. Cloud, Minnesota, Remarks at Saint Cloud University campus
  - November 15, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 249)
    St. Cloud, Minnesota, Remarks at Elephant Club
  - November 18, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 250)
    Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Remarks at Public Forum on Domestic Policy
  - November 18, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 251)
    Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Remarks at Benjamin Franklin Hotel
  - November 19, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 252)
    Washington, DC, Remarks at Fundraiser For Republican Congressman
  - November 20, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 253)
    Wichita, Kansas, Press Conference
  - November 20, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 254)
    Wichita, Kansas, GOP Reception
  - November 21, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 255)
    Wichita, Kansas, remarks at Republican Governors Conference
  - November 21, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 256)
    Wichita, Kansas, Q&A at Republican Governors Conference
  - November 25, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 257)
    Indianapolis, Indiana, Transcript, Public Forum on Domestic Policy
  - December 3, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 258)
    New York City, Statement before Moreland Commission
  - December 4, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 259)
    Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, remarks at Hilton Hotel
  - December 4, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 260)
    Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, remarks at Republican Awards Dinner
  - December 5, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 261)
    New York City, Remarks at National Association of Manufacturers
  - December 9, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 262)
    Los Angeles, California, Remarks at Public Forum
  - December 9, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 263)
    Los Angeles, California, TV Taping
  - December 10, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 264)
    Washington, DC, Mayflower Hotel, Remarks of VP at Council on Environmental Quality
  - December 10, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 265)
    Washington, DC, Remarks at National Center for Productivity and Quality of Working Life
  - December 11, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 266)
    Houston, Texas, Remarks at Black Republican Leadership
  - December 11, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 267)
  - December 11, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 268)
    Houston, Texas, Remarks at Houston Business and Professional Mens Club Dinner
  - December 11, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 269)
    Nashville, Tennessee, remarks at State Committee Lunch
  - December 11, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 270)
    Nashville, Tennessee, Press Conference at Metro Center
  - December 12, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 271)
    Houston, Texas, Remarks at Southern Republican Meeting
  - December 12, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 272)
    Houston, Texas, Remarks at Hyatt Regency
  - December 12, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 273)
    Houston, Texas, TV Taping at Hyatt Regency
  - December 17, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 274)
    Washington, DC, Press Conference on Domestic Council
  - December 17, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 275)
    Washington, DC, Remarks at President's Safety Award Meeting
  - January 14, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 276)
    Washington, DC, Remarks at National Councils of Farmers Cooperatives Shoreham America, Washington, D.C.
  - January 19, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 277)
    Washington, DC, Remarks at Opening Session of the 94th Congress
  - January 19, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 278)
    Washington, DC, Remarks at Water Quality hearings
  - January 20, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 279)
    Statement on conclusion of Water Quality Hearings
  - January 26, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 280)
    Remarks to Bolling Air Force Base Wives
  - January 26, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 281)
    Salem, West Virginia, Remarks at Salem College
  - January 26, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 282)
    Rye, New York, Remarks at Westchester City Republican Committee Dinner
  - January 30, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 283)
    Dearborn, Michigan, Press Conference at Hyatt Regency
  - January 30, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 284)
    Dearborn, Michigan, Remarks at GOP Reception
  - January 30, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 285)
    Dearborn, Michigan, Toast to Governor and Mrs. Milliken, Lovett Hall
  - February 2, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 286)
    Remarks at J. Paul Getty Wildlife Conservation Award Ceremony
  - February 3, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 287)
    Press Conference in White House Briefing Room
  - February 4, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 288)
    Letter to President dated 12/16/75
  - February 4, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 289)
    Remarks before Senate Committee on Government Operations
  - February 6, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 290)
    Washington DC, Twin Bridges, Marriott Hotel, Remarks at National Council of Arts
  - February 6, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 291)
    Washington DC, Twin Bridges, Marriott Hotel, Excerpts of remarks at North East Republican Leadership Lunch
  - February 6, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 292)
    Washington DC, Twin Bridges, Marriott Hotel, Introduction of President Ford at North East Republican Leadership Lunch
  - February 10, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 293)
    Washington DC, Remarks at Atomic Industry Forum
  - February 12, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 294)
    Louisville, Kentucky, Remarks at GOP Committee Meeting
  - February 12, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 295)
    Louisville, Kentucky, Remarks at GOP Lincoln Dinner
  - February 12, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 296)
    Louisville, Kentucky, TV Taping, Galt House
  - February 12, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 297)
    Louisville, Kentucky, Press Conference
  - February 14, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 298)
    New York City, Waldorf Astoria, Remarks at Lincoln Day Dinner
  - February 19, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 299)
    Washington, DC, Remarks at National Press Club Lunch
  - February 20, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 300)
    Lansing, Michigan, Remarks to Michigan State Republican Committee Bicentennial Dinner
  - February 20, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 301)
    Lansing, Michigan, Press Conference at Holiday Inn
  - February 23, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 302)
    Boston, Massachusetts, Remarks at American Association for Advancement of Science
  - February 24, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 303)
    Washington, DC, Statler Hilton, Remarks at National Governors Conference
  - February 25, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 304)
    Remarks at swearing-in of Arthur Fletcher, EOB
  - February 25, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 305)
    Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Remarks at Bicentennial Bishops and Connectional Church Council Banquet
  - March 4, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 306)
    Washington, DC, Interview with Richard Kershaw, BBC
  - March 4, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 307)
    Washington, DC, Interview with Martin Diamond
  - March 9, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 308)
    New York City, Remarks at Religion in American Life
  - March 10, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 309)
    Washington, DC, Jeff McMullen Interview / Australian Broadcasting Comm/Pre Trip Interview
  - March 10, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 310)
    National Industry Energy Council Department Of Commerce Pre-Trip Interview
  - March 12, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 311)
    Albuquerque, New Mexico, Remarks at GOP Lincoln Day Dinner
  - March 12, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 312)
    Albuquerque, New Mexico, Press conference
  - March 16, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 313)
    Chicago, Illinois, Remarks at National Association of Wholesale Grocers
  - March 17, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 314)
    Chicago, Illinois, Press Conference in Crystal Room
  - March 17, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 315)
    Chicago, Illinois, Remarks to Executive Club
  - March 17, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 316)
    Washington, DC, Remarks at Joint Economic Committee of Congress
  - March 18, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 317)
  - March 19, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 318)
    Remarks on Right of Privacy, Domestic Council
  - March 22, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 319)
    Paris, France, Press Conference at American Embassy
  - March 22, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 320)
    Paris, France, Bicentennial Address
  - March 29, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 321)
    Singapore, Toast by Vice President at Banquet
  - March 29, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 322)
    Singapore, Remarks to American Business Leaders' Reception
  - March 30, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 323)
    Canberra, Australia, Lake side Hotel, Press Conference
  - April 1, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 324)
    Sydney, Australia, Bicentennial Address, Wentworth Hotel
  - April 2, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 325)
    Wellington, New Zealand, Remarks at New Zealand State Luncheon
  - April 3, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 326)
    Wellington, New Zealand, Press Conference
  - April 7, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 327)
    Reston, Virginia, Remarks to National Energy Leadership Conference
  - April 8, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 328)
    Arlington, Virginia, WETZ-TV taping with Robert McNeil Report
  - April 12, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 329)
    Statement to Senate Committee re: S.2532, bill for Energy Independence Authority
  - April 12, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 330)
    Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Remarks at President Ford Committee Reception Urban Club
  - April 12, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 331)
    Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Remarks to Club of Rome
  - April 14, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 332)
    Des Moines, Iowa, Press Conference
  - April 14, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 333)
    Des Moines, Iowa, Remarks to Republican Dinner
  - April 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 334)
    Des Moines, Iowa, WHO-TV taping, Hotel Fort Des Moines
  - April 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 335)
  - April 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 336)
    Atlanta, Georgia, Remarks at HGOP Fundraising Reception, Peachtree Hotel
  - April 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 337)
    Atlanta, Georgia, Press Conference at Peachtree Plaza
  - April 18, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 338)
    Interview on "60 Minutes"
  - April 20, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 339)
    Washington, DC, Kennedy Center Remarks at President's Commission on Personnel Interchange Dinner
  - April 24, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 340)
    Exchange of telegrams by NAR and Senator Jackson
  - April 22, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 341)
    Senator Jackson Reply to telegram
  - April 29, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 342)
    Washington, DC Remarks at National Leadership Conference
  - April 28, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 343)
    Washington DC, Remarks at Annual Neptune Award Dinner
  - April 30, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 344)
    Remarks at George Washington Inaugural Ceremony, Washington Monument
  - May 2, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 345)
    Interview on "Issues and Answers," ABC
  - May 4, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 346)
    San Francisco, California, Press conference at Fairmont Hotel
  - May 4, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 347)
    San Francisco, California, Remarks to Commonwealth Club Lunch
  - May 5, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 348)
    Los Angeles California, Press Conference at Biltmore Hotel
  - May 7, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 349)
    Astoria, Queens, Remarks at Queens County Republican Dinner
  - May 10, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 350)
    Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Remarks to International Press Institute
  - May 10, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 351)
    Interview with German television Network, ARD
  - May 11, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 352)
    New York City, New York, Remarks at Accion International Dinner
  - May 13, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 353)
    Berlin, Germany, Arrival Statement
  - May 13, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 354)
    Italy, Udine Airport, Departure Statement
  - May 13, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 355)
    Italy, Udine Airport, Arrival Statement
  - May 14, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 356)
    Berlin, Germany, Remarks at Luncheon, Schloss Charlott
  - May 14, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 357)
    Berlin, Germany, Remarks at U.S. Mission Headquarters
  - May 14, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 358)
    Frankfurt, Germany, Arrival Statement, Am Main
  - May 14, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 359)
    Berlin, Germany, Departure Statement
  - May 14, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 360)
    Frankfurt, Germany, Remarks at Reception at City Hall
  - May 14, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 361)
    Frankfurt, Germany, Remarks at Frankfurt City Hall
  - May 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 362)
    Frankfurt, Germany, Remarks at Glass Exhibition
  - May 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 363)
    Frankfurt, Germany, Departure Statement
  - May 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 364)
    Frankfurt, Germany, Toast, Schloss Kronberg Lunch
  - May 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 365)
  - May 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 366)
  - May 15, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 367)
    Frankfurt, Germany, Texts of Remarks at Frankfurt Am Main at Paulskirche
  - May 17, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 368)
    Exchange of remarks between President, VP and Daniel Parker in Oval Office
  - May 19, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 369)
    Yorktown, New York, Remarks at Bicentennial Ceremony
  - May 20, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 370)
    Cincinnati, Ohio, Remarks at PFC Committee Dinner, Quenn City Club
  - May 23, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 371)
    Newport, Rhode Island, Remarks at 50th Anniversary of the Synagogue Council of America
  - May 30, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 372)
    New York City, New York, Transcript of Face the Nation
  - June 2, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 373)
    Colorado Springs, Colorado, Remarks at Air Force Academy
  - June 2, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 374)
    Colorado Springs, Colorado, Press Conference
  - June 3, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 375)
    Office of VP, Immediate Release RE: Reagan/Rhodesia
  - June 4, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    Ocean City, Maryland, Maryland State Republican Dinner
  - June 4, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 377)
  - June 9, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 378)
    Washington, DC, Remarks at National Editorial Association
  - June 16, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 379)
    Washington, DC, Remarks at National Housing Conference